HARINI R

1/53, Namus PG for Ladies , Stage 1, BTM layout, Bengaluru, karnataka - 560094 harinichweet882@yahoo.com | 6385699228

OBJECTIVE

Self-motivated individual with (1.8+ years) of Experience into HR domain a knack for critical thinking and developing solutions that are not only scalable but also easy to implement. Creative individual with the ability to understand day to day issues faced by management and employees. Seeing to revolutionize the HR Management and Activities by Implementing New Processes and working outside the box.

EXPERIENCE

• Provab Technosoft Pvt. Ltd, Bengaluru (Trainee)

May 2023 - Aug 2023

HR Trainee

Sourcing, Screening, Shortlisting, Recruiting, Hiring, IT Recruitment, Non-IT Recruitment, Clients handling, Interview Scheduling, Coordinating, Induction, Onboarding, End to End Recruitment.

Amazon Development Center, Bengaluru (Contract)

May 2022 - Nov 2022

HR Assistant

HR - CTK (Centralized time keeping) department, Time and Attendance Management, Leave Management, Grievance handling, Maintaining Employee Database, Induction, Training and Development, Employee Engagement, Team Management.

• Ola (Ani Technologies), Bengaluru

Jan 2020 - June 2020

CVT Executive (Central Verification Team)

Verifying and Validating Clients Documents and Performing Background Checks (BGV).

EDUCATION

ANNAMALAI UNIVERSITY, CHIDAMBARAM	2022
M.B.A in (Human Resource Management)	
81% (with Distinction)	
P.S.V COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY, KRISHNAGIRI	2018
B.E in (Computer Science Engineering)	
70%	
BHARAT MATRIC HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL, KRISHNAGIRI	2014
HSC	
73.5%	
BHARAT MATRIC HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL, KRISHNAGIRI	2012
SSLC	
83.2%	
	M.B.A in (Human Resource Management) 81% (with Distinction) P.S.V COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY, KRISHNAGIRI B.E in (Computer Science Engineering) 70% BHARAT MATRIC HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL, KRISHNAGIRI HSC 73.5% BHARAT MATRIC HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL, KRISHNAGIRI SSLC

SKILLS

- Induction, Onboarding & Joining Formalities
- End To End Recruitment
- · Hiring, Screening & Shortlisting
- · Scheduling & Coordinating Interviews
- · Employee Engagement
- Grievance Handling
- · Communication Processes
- · Client's Handling
- Leave Management

- Team Management
- · Time and Attendance Management
- · HR Operations
- Employee BGV Verification & Validation
- Training and Development

PROJECTS

• IOT Based Smart Irrigation And Monitoring System In Cloud Computing

Using the Smart irrigation we can imporove the agriculture and monitoring the live data streams of land and soil in cloud computing

INTERESTS

- Human Resources Generalist
- · Planning and organizing
- Leadership
- Labour Laws
- · Performance management
- · Benefits and compensation
- Payroll Processing
- HR Coordinator
- End To End HR Activities

STRENGTH

- Multitasking
- Problem Solving
- · Independent And Bold
- · Interpersonal skills
- · Decision Making

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Father's Name: M. Ramesh

Nationality : Indian Gender : Female

Marital status: Spinster

Language: English, Tamil, Kannada, Telugu

DECLARATION

• I hereby declare that the information are correct and true to my knowledge and belief

Signature: